{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "English for Academic & Professional Purposes",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Combined Prelims Reviewer",
    "LastModified": "16 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What are specialized, formal pieces of writing, crafted by experts within a specific field?",
      "answer": "Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Text",
        "Persuasive Text",
        "Analytical Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is characterized by their use of objective language, evidence-based arguments, and adherence to a structured format?",
      "answer": "Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Text",
        "Persuasive Text",
        "Descriptive Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What aims to inform, analyze, or persuade a scholarly audience, relying on research and data to support claims?",
      "answer": "Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Text",
        "Analytical Text",
        "Critical Academic Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What usually delivers simple and basic information?",
      "answer": "Non-Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Text",
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Descriptive Text",
        "Social Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Non-Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can be read and easily understood by any kind of reader?",
      "answer": "Non-Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Text",
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Social Language",
        "Persuasive Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Non-Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is personal, emotional, impressionistic, or subjective in nature?",
      "answer": "Non-Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Text",
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Language",
        "Critical Academic Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Non-Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text provides facts and information?",
      "answer": "Descriptive",
      "choices": [
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Descriptive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text organizes facts and information into categories, groups, parts, types or relationships?",
      "answer": "Analytical",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text includes argument, recommendation, interpretation, or evaluation of the work of others with the addition of your own point of view?",
      "answer": "Persuasive",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text needs to be supported by evidence?",
      "answer": "Persuasive",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text requires you to consider at least two points of view, including your own?",
      "answer": "Critical academic text",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical academic text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the language needed by students to do the work in schools?",
      "answer": "Academic Language",
      "choices": [
        "Social Language",
        "Academic Language",
        "Formal Language",
        "Informal Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Language Types"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the set of vocabulary that allows us to communicate with others in the context of regular daily conversations?",
      "answer": "Social Language",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Language",
        "Social Language",
        "Informal Language",
        "Formal Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Language Types"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the basic structure that is used by an academic text is consist of three (3) parts introduction, body, and conclusion which is formal and logical?",
      "answer": "Structure",
      "choices": [
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation",
        "Structure"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What enables the reader to follow the argument and navigate the text?",
      "answer": "Structure",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the attitude conveyed in a piece of writing?",
      "answer": "Tone",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should be used for the arguments of others to be fairly presented and with an appropriate narrative tone?",
      "answer": "Tone",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What enables a reader to follow your line of thinking without difficulty?",
      "answer": "Clear topic sentences",
      "choices": [
        "Unambiguous language",
        "Clear topic sentences",
        "Third person point-of-view",
        "Formal language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a very important aspect of an academic text for citing sources in the body of the paper and providing a list of references as either footnotes or endnotes?",
      "answer": "Citation",
      "choices": [
        "Citation",
        "Structure",
        "Language",
        "Tone"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the starting point of an academic text is a particular perspective, idea or position applied to the chosen research problem?",
      "answer": "Thesis-driven",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Thesis-driven",
        "Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a strategy that readers use to recall prior knowledge and set a purpose for reading?",
      "answer": "Preview",
      "choices": [
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Preview",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What means not only recognizing words, word order, and patterns, but also generating meaning through analysis and evaluation?",
      "answer": "Read and Understand",
      "choices": [
        "Preview",
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is used to express the most important facts or ideas about something or someone in a short and clear form?",
      "answer": "Summarize",
      "choices": [
        "Preview",
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is used to restate your overall opinions of the text?",
      "answer": "Review",
      "choices": [
        "Preview",
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the presentation of another's works or ideas as if they were your own without giving credit to the other person?",
      "answer": "Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the word-for-word transcription of a section of someone else's work, without attribution and without quotation marks?",
      "answer": "Direct Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when a student submits his or her own previous work, or mixes parts of previous works, without permission from all professors involved?",
      "answer": "Self Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when a student borrows phrases from a source without using quotation marks, or finds synonyms for the author's language while keeping to the same general structure?",
      "answer": "Mosaic Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when a person neglects to cite their sources, or misquotes their sources, or unintentionally paraphrases a source by using similar words without attribution?",
      "answer": "Accidental Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves copying off of someone else's exam?",
      "answer": "Cheating",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves making up the results for a lab exercise?",
      "answer": "Fabrication",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves submitting the same paper for two classes?",
      "answer": "Multiple Submissions",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves letting a roommate copy your homework?",
      "answer": "Facilitating Academic Dishonesty",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Facilitating Academic Dishonesty",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a form of communication that is shaped by factors?",
      "answer": "Writing",
      "choices": [
        "Outlining",
        "Writing",
        "Thesis Statement",
        "Topic Sentence"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Writing Process"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the overall idea or arguments of your work?",
      "answer": "Thesis statement",
      "choices": [
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Thesis statement",
        "Outline",
        "Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Key Writing Components"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a general statement that presents essential points that leads the reader to the right direction?",
      "answer": "Thesis statement",
      "choices": [
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Thesis statement",
        "Outline",
        "Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Key Writing Components"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is included as a sentence or as part of the text?",
      "answer": "Explicit Thesis Statement",
      "choices": [
        "Implicit Thesis Statement",
        "Explicit Thesis Statement",
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Traditional Outline"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Thesis Statements"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is it when the primary point of the reading is conveyed indirectly, in multiple locations throughout the work?",
      "answer": "Implicit Thesis Statement",
      "choices": [
        "Explicit Thesis Statement",
        "Implicit Thesis Statement",
        "Topic Sentence",
        "Standard Outline"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Thesis Statements"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a tool we use in the writing process to help organize our ideas, visualize our paper's potential structure?",
      "answer": "Outlining",
      "choices": [
        "Outlining",
        "Clustering",
        "Brainstorming",
        "Free Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Pre-writing Stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a step to produce ideas for writing that groups the ideas according to their relevance?",
      "answer": "Outlining",
      "choices": [
        "Clustering",
        "Outlining",
        "Brainstorming",
        "Free Writing"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Pre-writing Stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of outline uses roman numerals, letters and numbers?",
      "answer": "Traditional Outline",
      "choices": [
        "Standard Outline",
        "Traditional Outline",
        "Parallelism",
        "Subordination"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Kinds of Outline"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of outline uses numbers?",
      "answer": "Standard Outline",
      "choices": [
        "Standard Outline",
        "Traditional Outline",
        "Coordination",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Kinds of Outline"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should observe the same language structure?",
      "answer": "Parallelism",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should observe level of importance?",
      "answer": "Coordination",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should observe differences of importance?",
      "answer": "Subordination",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle of outlining is it when entries should at least be two to be sure that supporting points of a major idea are adequate?",
      "answer": "Division",
      "choices": [
        "Coordination",
        "Subordination",
        "Parallelism",
        "Division"
      ],
      "reference": "L3-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Principles of Outlining"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an essay of your thoughts about something that could be a movie, book, incident, etc.?",
      "answer": "Reflection Paper",
      "choices": [
        "Reaction Paper",
        "Critique Paper",
        "Reflection Paper",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Papers"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a task that requires a student to analyze information and give comments on a certain text or media?",
      "answer": "Reaction Paper",
      "choices": [
        "Reflection Paper",
        "Reaction Paper",
        "Critique Paper",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Papers"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a specific style of essay in which you identify, evaluate, and respond to an author's ideas, both positively and negatively?",
      "answer": "Critique Paper",
      "choices": [
        "Reflection Paper",
        "Reaction Paper",
        "Critique Paper",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Papers"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reflection paper contains the idea and thesis statement?",
      "answer": "Introduction",
      "choices": [
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Introduction",
        "Analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reflection Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reflection paper explains the introduction and may include quotes and passages?",
      "answer": "Body",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Comments"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reflection Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reflection paper wraps up the paper and describes the feeling and overall lesson?",
      "answer": "Conclusion",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Suggestion"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reflection Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reaction paper introduces the work to the reader by giving the name of the author and what the work is about?",
      "answer": "Details of the Work",
      "choices": [
        "The Context",
        "The Need and Reaction",
        "Details of the Work",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reaction Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reaction paper gives the background of the piece you are reacting to?",
      "answer": "The Context",
      "choices": [
        "The Context",
        "The Need and Reaction",
        "Details of the Work",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reaction Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reaction paper includes your opinion, thoughts, or ideas about the work?",
      "answer": "The Need and Reaction",
      "choices": [
        "The Context",
        "The Need and Reaction",
        "Details of the Work",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reaction Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a critique paper describes the work or piece you are critiquing?",
      "answer": "Introduction",
      "choices": [
        "Analysis",
        "Comments and Suggestions",
        "Introduction",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Critique Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a critique paper provides the critique and detailed analysis of the work?",
      "answer": "Analysis",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Analysis",
        "Comments and Suggestions",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Critique Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a critique paper points out the things that may give improvements to the work you are critiquing?",
      "answer": "Comments and Suggestions",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Analysis",
        "Comments and Suggestions",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Critique Paper"
    }
  ]
}